paribus.co 2015-03-15

# Paribus.co | Get money back on your online purchases

Your privacy matters to us. We aim to provide you with information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, respect your privacy. We’ve crafted the policy below to be as clear and straightforward as possible. Please feel free to contact us with any questions or feedback at [support@paribus.co](mailto:support@paribus.co). 

## 1\. Introduction

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers how Paribus Co. (“we,” “us,” “our,” and “Paribus”) treats Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") and other information that Paribus collects in connection with its websites, mobile applications, platforms, premium services, or any content or information provided as part of the Paribus services (collectively, “Paribus” or the “Services”). 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your registration or use of any part of the Services will constitute your notice about and agreement to our collection and use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to us collecting or using your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, do not use the Services and close your account.

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, and if we make material changes to it, we will provide notice through our Services, or by other means so that you may review the changes before you continue to use the Services. If you object to any changes, you may close your account. Continuing to use the Services after we publish or communicate a notice about any changes to this Privacy Policy means that you are consenting to the changes.

## 2\. Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through the Services. It does not apply to information collected elsewhere, including, without limitation, offline or on sites linked to through the Services. It does not apply to any third-party activities, such as third-party websites linked from our Services, third-party social networking platforms, or third-party ads displayed on our Services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of third parties. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of those third parties.

We consider PII to be information that can be traced directly back to and identifies a specific individual or household, such as name, physical address, email address, phone number, or billing information. We do not consider PII to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not allow a third party to easily identify a specific individual or household. Paribus does not share PII with non-affiliated third parties except as specified in Section 4.5, Section 4.7, and Section 4.8 

## 3\. The Information We Collect From You

### 3.1. Registration and connecting your Accounts

Paribus collects information when you register. Paribus may ask for your name, password, email address, and billing information, including, credit card number, expiration date, and associated physical address.

Paribus also collects information when you connect your email address, social network, or other Internet account (collectively, “Accounts”) with the Services. This information generally includes, but is not limited to, your name, and email address. It may also include, but is not limited to, your login credentials, website ID, public profile with the service, and demographic information. 

Upon connecting your Accounts with the Services, Paribus may scan your emails and collect information from your Accounts relating to your online purchases, offline purchases, shopping history, and any information necessary to further the Services

We may use and share this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.

### 3.2. Profile Information

After you create an account, you may choose to provide additional information on your Paribus profile 

We may use and share information you provide in your profile in accordance with this Privacy and our Terms of Service.

### 3.3 Using the Services

Paribus collects information for anyone who uses the Services, not just registered users. Even if you’re not logged into the Services, we may collect your IP address, device identifier, browser type, device type, mobile phone carrier, domain name, access times, duration of visit, referring URL, platform, new and repeat information, time stamp, exit page information, geolocation, and other information about how you use the Services.

Paribus also collects information from your Accounts as long as your Accounts are connected to the Services. Paribus may scan your emails and collect information from your Accounts relating to your online purchases, offline purchases, shopping history, and any information necessary to further the Services.

Paribus also collects information when you submit a claim for a partial refund/credit to a third party. In order to submit a claim, we may ask for your billing information, including, credit card number, expiration date, and associated physical address. 

We may use and share this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.

### 3.4 Customer Service

When you contact our customer support services, we collect information that helps us categorize your question, respond to it, and, if applicable, investigate any breach of our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy. We also use this information to track potential problems and trends and customize our support responses to better serve you.

### 3.5. Cookies, Advertising Technologies, and Web Beacons

We may use cookies and similar technologies to help us recognize you across the Services, improve your Paribus experience, increase security, measure use and effectiveness of our Services, and serve advertising. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. By using the Services, you consent to the placement of cookies and beacons in your browser and HTML-based emails in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### 3.6 Other

Paribus seeks to improve the services we offer you. We often introduce new features, some of which may result in the collection of new information. Furthermore, new partnerships or corporate acquisitions may result in new features, and we may potentially collect new types of information.

## 4\. How we use your Personal Information

### 4.1 Consent to Paribus Processing Information About You

By registering with or using the Services, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of the Terms of Service and freely accepting and agreeing to our processing of your information in ways set out by this Privacy Policy. 

Supplying to us any information is entirely voluntary on your part. You have the right to withdraw or modify your consent to Paribus’ collection and processing of the PII you provide at any time, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service, consistent with Section 5.1

### 4.2 Paribus Communications

The information you provide us allows us to communicate with you. We may communicate with you through email, notices posted on the Services, and other means available through the Services. Examples of these communications include: (1) welcome and engagement communications; (2) service communications covering service availability, security, and other issues about the functioning of the Services; and (3) promotional communications that may contain promotional information from us or third parties. You can opt out of promotional messages by sending a request to [support@paribus.co](mailto:support@paribus.co). Please be aware that you cannot opt out of receiving service messages from Paribus.

### 4.3 Customized Content and Improved Experience

We use the information that you provide to us to customize content and improve your user experience. For example, information regarding your online purchases, offline purchases, and shopping history allows us monitor price changes for products you purchased and file claims on your behalf. 

We also use the information that you provide us to improve our products and services for all users, conduct research, and develop and maintain anonymous and aggregated data and analytics. For example, information regarding your online purchases, aggregated with the information of other users, allows us to decipher industry wide trends.

### 4.4. Sharing Information with Affiliates

We may share your PII with our Paribus affiliates (meaning entities controlled by, controlling or under common control with Paribus) as necessary to provide the Services. By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are consenting to this sharing. 

Any Paribus affiliate will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.

### 4.5. Sharing Information with Service Providers

We may employ third parties and individuals to develop, improve, and/or facilitate our Services (e.g. maintenance, analysis, audit, marketing and development). These third parties have limited access to your PII only to perform these tasks on our behalf.

You recognize and agree that these third parties may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other services or products relating to your activities. Paribus is not responsible for any information these companies have independently collected and used under their own privacy policies.

### 4.6. Sharing Information with Third Parties

Paribus does not share PII with non-affiliated third parties except as specified in Section 4.5, Section 4.7, and Section 4.8 

We may share anonymous and aggregated information and analytics relating to you with third parties. Such information may be of value to third parties in the performance of marketing services, including evaluating market trends and/or under a joint marketing agreement to provide services that will be of particular interest and relevance to you. When you deactivate your Paribus account, your PII is permanently disassociated with your purchase information. We may continue to use and share any anonymous and aggregated information and analytics relating to you.

When you deactivate your Paribus account, your PII is permanently disassociated with your purchase data. The anonymized purchase data itself may continue to be incorporated in market analyses.

### 4.7 Compliance with Legal Process and Other Disclosures

It is possible that we may need to disclose your PII to third parties when required by law, subpoena, or other legal process, or if Paribus has a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (1) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies; (2) enforce the Terms of Service, investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, or protect the security or integrity of our Services; or (3) exercise or protect the rights, property, or safety of Paribus, our users, personnel, or others. We attempt to notify users about legal demands for their data when appropriate in our judgment, unless prohibited by law or court order or when the request is an emergency. In light of our principles, we may dispute such demands when we believe, in our discretion, that the requests are overboard, vague or lack proper authority, but do not commit to challenge every demand. 

### 4.8 Disclosure to Others as the Result of a Change in Control or Sale of Paribus Co

We may disclose your PII to a third party as part of a transfer or sale of the assets of Paribus Co., a subsidiary, or division, or as the result of a change in control of the company or one of its affiliates, or in preparation for any of these events.

Any third party to which Paribus transfers or sells Paribus’ assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.

## 5\. Your Information

### 5.1 Rights to Access, Correct, or Delete Your Information, and Closing Your Account

You have a right to (1) access, modify, correct, or delete your PII controlled by Paribus; and (2) close your account. You can access, modify, correct, or delete your PII by sending an email to [support@paribus.co](mailto:support@paribus.co), specifying the request sought with proof of identity. If you close your account(s), your information will generally be removed from the Services within 10 business days. We generally delete closed account information and will de-personalize any logs or other backup information within 30 days of account closure, except as noted below. You may not be able to access, correct, or eliminate any information that is not in our control. 

### 5.2 Data Retention

We retain the PII you provide while your account is in existence or as needed to provide you the Services. Paribus may retain your PII even after you have closed your account if retention is reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes between users, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. We may retain personal information, for a limited period of time, if requested by law enforcement. Paribus’ Customer Service may retain information for as long as is necessary to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis only, but we generally delete or de-personalize closed account data consistent with Section 5.1.

## 6\. Important Information

### 6.1. Minimum Age

As described in Section 3.1 of the Terms of Service, persons must be of Minimum Age to use Paribus. 

### 6.2. Change to the Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make significant changes in the way we treat your personal information, or to the Privacy Policy, we will provide notice to you on the Services or by some other means, such as email. Please review the changes carefully. If you agree to the changes, simply continue to use our Services. If you object to any of the changes to our terms and you no longer wish to use Paribus, you may close your account(s). Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that Paribus has about you and your account. Using the Services after a notice of changes has been communicated to you or published on our Services shall constitute consent to the changed terms or practices.

### 6.3. Security

Paribus limits access to your PII. We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in an effort to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and use correctly the PII we collect from you.

No data transmissions through the Internet or mobile devices, or even the physical transfer of information, are completely secure. We cannot fully eliminate all security risks associated with personal information, and technical mistakes are possible. We do not ensure or warrant the security of any data or information you transmit to us and any information you disclose to us is at your own risk. Please help keep your account safe by using a strong password.

If Paribus learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically. You agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues. We may post a notice on our website if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view and access Paribus. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), you should notify us at [support@paribus.co](mailto:support@paribus.co). 

### 6.4 International Visitors

Paribus is located in and intended for use in the United States by United States residents. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your PII to the United States to Paribus. By providing your PII, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 6.5. Contact Information

If you have questions or suggestions, please email Paribus at [support@paribus.co](mailto:support@paribus.co).
